A Finding Aid to the Garry Knox Bennett Papers, 1917-2017, bulk 1960-2017, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Made in Oakland: The Furniture of Garry Knox Bennett Retrospective, circa 1977-2009; Series 5; Archival Resource Key; 1.5 Linear feet Boxes 9-11
  - Lenders, G, 1996-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Lenders, H-J, 1977-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Lenders, Peter Joseph, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Lenders, K, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Lenders, L, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 6-7)
  - Lenders, Sydney Lewis, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 8-10)
  - Lenders, T, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Lenders, V-Z, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Lenders, General, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Loan Agreements, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Oakland Museum, 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Photographs and Slides, Regarding, 1995-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 16-17)
  - Publicity, 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Renwick Gallery / Kenneth Trapp, 1996-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Shipping Labels, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Financial and Legal Records, 1950s-2010; Series 6; Archival Resource Key; 0.5 Linear feet Boxes 11-12
  Series includes card files containing sales information from Bennett's early works, invoices and receipts, check registers, and legal records for the estate of Peter T. Joseph.
  - Check Registers, 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 21)
    3 registers
  - Estate of Peter T. Joseph Legal Records, 1995-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 22-23)
  - Financial Records, General, 1981-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Invoice Book, 1979-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Invoice, Cable Tension Gluing Process Patent, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Invoices and Receipts, Shipping, 1990-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
  - Invoices, Photography Services, 1983-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Sales, Card File, 1950s-1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 4-6)
- Printed Materials, 1960-2015; Series 7; Archival Resource Key; 0.8 Linear feet Box 12
  Series includes clippings, event programs, announcements and catalogs for exhibitions of work by Bennett and others, invitations, and some miscellaneous items.
  - Clippings, General, circa 1980-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, A-Z, circa 1975-circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 8-11)
    Clippings are arranged in rough alphabetical order by author name.
  - Event Program, 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, Bennett, circa 1974-2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 13-14)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, Others, 1968-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Exhibition History Material, circa 1999-2015; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Invitations, 1960-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous, 1953-2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Scrapbooks, 1948-1997; Series 8; Archival Resource Key; 0.4 Linear feet Boxes 12-13
  The scrapbooks contain mainly printed exhibition materials and clippings pertaining to Bennett's career. Some personal items such as letters, photographs, and documents from Bennett's youth can be found in the unbound material.
  - Scrapbook (1-2 of 3), circa 1960-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 2-3)
  - Scrapbook, Loose Material (3 of 3), circa 1960-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Scrapbook, Unbound Material, 1948-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Scrapbook, Unbound Material, 1996-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 21)